太棒了
All right!
从家里赶到医院 花了不到七分钟的时间，我们办到了
Yes! From home to the hospital in under seven minutes! We did it.
对，最难的部份完成了
Yes,the hard part is truly over.
不，但打起精神来 我们有个不错的开始，对吧？
No,but come on,we're off to a great start,aren't we?
我知道我可以很快赶到这里 但这一定是创下了记录
I knew I'd get here fast,but this has gotta be some kind of a record!
-你们赶到了 -嗨
-Oh,you made it! -Hi.
-你们怎么会比我们先到？ -我们搭计程车，你们是走过来的吗？
-How the hell did you beat us here? -We took a cab. Did you guys walk?
不，我们也是搭计程车 但我做过实验…
No,we took a cab too. But I did test runs..
你们赶到了
Hey,you made it!
好吧，难不成有魔法地道 通到这家医院？
Okay,is there some kind of magic tunnel to this hospital?
罗斯，你留下来聊天 我要去生孩子了
Ross,you stay here and talk. I'm gonna go have a baby.
好吧，她是瑞秋格林 我是罗斯盖勒，我们在车上打过电话
Okay. Hi,this is Rachel Greene. I'm Ross Geller. We called from the car.
对，我们为你们准备了 双人待产室，所以…
Right. We have a semi-private labor room waiting for you,so..
对不起，双人房？ 我们订了单人房
Oh,whoa! I'm sorry. Semi-private? We asked for a private room.
我知道，不幸地是 我们无法保证一定有单人房
Yes,I see that here. Unfortunately,we can't guarantee a private room.
-现在单人房都满了 -你该快点过来的
-And,currently,they're all unavailable. -Man,if only you'd gotten here sooner.
抱歉 我们只有双人待产室
I'm sorry. Semi-private rooms are all we have.
好吧，等我们一下，罗斯
Okay. Just give us a second. Ross?
什么？
Yeah?
-塞点钱给她 -我真的相信他们没房间了
-Give her some money. -I really think they're out of rooms.
才怪，罗斯 他们为大人物保留房间
They're not,Ross. They're just saving them for important people!
好吧？如果我是总统呢？
Okay? What if I was the president?
那么我们麻烦大了 你不知道任何国家的地理位置
Well,then,we'd be in a lot of trouble. You don't know where any countries are.
好吧
Okay.
你能再帮我们看看吗？
Say,would you mind checking again?
有没有我们可以使用的 单人待产室？
See if any private rooms may have opened up?
这里是医院
This is a hospital.
我懂了 我们能跟经理谈一谈吗？
Okay,I see. Could we please talk to the manager?
这里没有经理
There is no manager.
只有护士、医生 跟双人待产室
Just nurses,doctors and semi-private rooms.
好吧，你知道吗？我得说 我真的不在乎你的语气
Okay,you know what? I have to say,I don't really care for your tone.
这是市里唯一一家医院 我们没有问题…天啊
And this is not the only hospital in this city,and we have no problem.. Oh,gosh!
-什么？ -是阵痛
-What? What? -Contraction!
-你们想看看双人待产室吗？ -好吧，看看又何妨
-Would you like to see a semi-private room? -Yeah,it couldn't hurt to look.
本集播出：瑞秋生产记
The.One.Where.Rachel.Has.a.Baby
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
主演：寇妮考克斯
主演：丽莎库卓
主演：麦特勒布兰
主演：马修派瑞
主演：大卫修蒙
你只开了两公分 得等到开十公分才行
Well,you're only two centimeters dilated,and we need to get to 10.
-那得等上一段时间 -好吧
-It'll be a while. -Oh,okay.
-我一小时后再回来帮你检查 -谢谢
-I'll be back in an hour to check you again. -Thank you.
等一下，朗医生 我能问你一件事吗？
Oh,wait,Dr. Long. Can I ask you something?
生产真的跟大家说的一样 那么痛吗？
Is labor really as painful as everybody says it is?
天啊 我的呼叫器响个不停
Oh,look at that. My beeper's going crazy.
别…你知道吗？ 你会没事的
Hey,don't.. You know what? You're gonna be fine.
-我猜我们得想办法消磨时间 -没错
-I guess we have some time to kill. -Yeah,guess so.
你看
Oh,check these out.
我从来没有这么做过
Never done this before.
不觉得很舒服
Doesn't feel good.
对，它看起来很不错
Yeah,well,it looks great.
谢谢 我想我们准备好…
Thank you very much. I think we're ready to..
嗨，我是罗斯 我来帮你们毁了这美好的一天
Hi,I'm Ross. I'm here to ruin this magical day for you.
一点都不会，没关系的，马克何格 她是我太太茱莉
Oh,no,not at all. It's okay. Marc Horger. This is my wife,Julie.
-嗨，茱莉，她是瑞秋 -嗨，瑞秋
-Hi,Julie. This is Rachel. -Oh,hi,Rachel.
-这是你的第一胎？ -对
-Is this your first? -Yeah,it is.
小吉米是我们的第三胎
Well,little Jamie here is our third.
如果你们有问题 或需要帮忙，叫我们一声
So if you have any questions,or you need anything at all,just holler.
-那真的是太棒了 -对
-That's so sweet. -Yeah.
-我得给你们私人空间 -没关系，我们可以一起
-Let me give you guys some privacy. -Nonsense. We're all in this together.
我们愿意 跟你们分享每一刻
We are gonna share every moment of this with you.
-我想我们会非常愉快 -对
-I think we're gonna have some fun. -Yeah.
-我猜好吧 -笑一个
-Oh,okay,I guess. -Hey,smile!
-我不知道… -我真的不要…
-I don't know if.. -I really don't want any..
谢谢
Oh,thank you.
罗斯 我又开始阵痛了
Oh,Ross! Here comes another contraction.
好吧，深呼吸
Okay,just breathe.
-亲爱的，我想我也开始阵痛了 -天啊
-Oh,honey,I think I'm having one too! -Oh,my God!
你看
Hey,look at this.
-来吧 -不
-Here you go! -Oh,no!
三个小时还是没生
Oh,wow. Three hours and still no baby.
生产的奇迹 的确让人很想打瞌睡
The miracle of birth sure is a snooze-fest.
-你要看看好玩的事吗？ -当然要，什么？
-Hey,you wanna see something? -Sure. What?
这一定会很好玩 看我怎么吓钱德
This is gonna be fun. Watch me freak out Chandler.
-亲爱的 -什么？
-Honey? -Yeah?
听着 我一直在想…
Listen,I've been doing some thinking..
我不知道是因为 我们来到这里…
and I don't know whether it's because we're here..
或是瑞秋要生孩子…
or Rachel's giving birth..
但我想我们应该试着怀孕
but I think we should try to have a baby.
好吧
Okay.
你说什么？
What's that now?
好吧，我也一直在想那件事 我想我们准备好了
Okay. I've been thinking about it too,and I think we're ready.
你在开玩笑吗？ 你觉得我们准备好要怀孕了？
Are you kidding? You think we're ready to have a baby now?
这真的很好玩
This is fun.
你们准备要怀孕了？ 我的小男孩长大了
You're ready to have a baby? My boy's all grown up!
你说你也准备好了
You said you were ready too.
对，我只是想跟你开玩笑 让你用高八度的怪声音说话…
Yeah,but I was just screwing with you to try to get your voice all high and weird..
就像我现在一样
Like mine is now!
对，但你不是一直 都想要生孩子吗？
Yes,but haven't you wanted a kid,like,forever?
对，但没有人 想跟我生孩子，我是说…
Yeah,but no one ever wanted to have one with me. I mean..
如果我要的话，我要生个孩子 你对我做了什么？
Now I'm just gonna have a baby if I want to. Oh,what are you doing to me?
抱歉我提起这件事
I'm sorry I brought it up.
好吧，滚开，先生
Okay,then,back off,mister!
因为我准备生孩子了
Because I am ready to have a baby.
我只是希望乔伊是孩子的爸
I just want Joey to be the father.
-什么？你疯了吗？ -就是那样，那就是我的目地
-What? Are you crazy? -That's it,right there! That's all I wanted!
抱歉，医生刚才非得拉上布帘做检查
I am sorry. The doctor insisted on closing the curtain for the exam.
那非常… 真的没关系
Oh,that's very.. Really,very,very okay.
茱莉的子宫颈开了七公分 大约是四指宽
Julie's cervix is dilated seven centimeters. That's about four fingers!
-医生让我自己摸摸看 -你摸过瑞秋的子宫颈吗？罗斯
-Doctor let me feel it myself. -Have you felt Rachel's cervix,Ross?
-没有…我们不会那么做 -我们不会那么做
-No,I don't.. We're not gonna do that. -We won't be doing that.
如果你要的话，你可以摸摸瑞秋的 再摸摸我的做比较
Well,if you like,you could feel Rachel's,then feel mine to compare.
-我打扰了你们吗？ -太棒了，谢谢，待会见
-Am I interrupting? -Yes! Thank you! Later.
-不，你不能丢下我跟他们独处 -对不起
-No,you can't leave me alone with them. -Oh,I'm sorry.
不，罗斯 我的孩子没有父亲
No,Ross? Ross? Ross? My child has no father!
我很高兴你来了 可能还要再等一下，你该先打电话来
I'm so glad you're here,but it's gonna be a while. I wish you'd called first.
没关系 我待会会再跟你爸来一趟
That's all right. I'm coming back later with your father.
-在孩子出生前我得跟你谈一谈 -好吧，什么事？
-I needed to talk to you before the birth. -Okay. What's up?
罗斯，我得用妈妈的身份 跟你谈…
Ross,I want to talk to you as your mother..
即使我知道 你跟我也是好朋友
even though I know that you and I are also very close friends.
我真的不知道你在说什么 但没关系
I really don't know what you're talking about,but okay.
我有样东西要给你
I brought something that I want to give you.
假设你真的要它
Assuming,of course,that you want it.
妈，你要我娶你？
Ma,you're asking me to marry you?
这是你外婆的订婚戒指 我要你把它送给瑞秋
This is your grandmother's engagement ring,I want you to give it to Rachel.
-妈，不，别这样，谢谢你 -听我说…
-Mom,no. Come on. Thank you. -Just hear me out..
不，好吗？我们谈过了
No! Okay? We've been through this.
我们不会因为她怀孕了 就去结婚，好吗？
We're not gonna get married just because she's pregnant. Okay?
说真的，罗斯 她不是你在酒吧泡到就上的女孩
Honestly,Ross,this isn't just some girl you picked up in a bar and humped.
年轻人比我们 更常用那个字
You think young people use that word more than we actually do.
罗斯，孩子应该要有家庭
Ross,a child should have a family.
你知道吗？ 我现在无法思考此事，抱歉
You know what? I can't deal with this right now. I'm sorry.
去…去跟莫妮卡聊一聊
Go.. Hey,go talk to Monica.
她换了新发型 你会讨厌的
She got a new haircut. You'll hate it.
考虑一下，如果你不那么做 我会再跟你谈上女孩的事
Just think about it. If you don't,I'll talk more about humping.
给我吧
Give me.
-嗨，亲爱的 -谢谢你赶过来
-Hi,dear. -Hi. Thank you so much for coming.
罗斯，快进来
Ross,get in here!
你想看好笑的事吗？
You wanna see something funny?
莫妮卡
Monica.
好吧，别闹了 你把我吓坏了
Okay. All right,stop it. You're freaking me out.
再来一次
Do it again. Do it again.
瑞秋生了
Hey,Rachel had the baby.
-什么？ -真的吗？
-What? -Really?
不
No.
我不知道为什么 我会觉得那很好笑
I don't know why I thought that'd be funny.
妈走之前 你跟她打过招呼吧？
You said hi to Mom before she left,right?
我就知道是她
I thought that was her.
我叫了她 她躲进楼梯间里
Yeah,I called her name,and she ducked into a stairwell.
你知道吗？你真的很幸运
Well,you know what? Consider yourself lucky.
她把我拖出待产室 问我为什么不跟瑞秋结婚
She pulled me out of the labor room to ask me why I'm not with Rachel.
-天啊 -那一定很烦
-Oh,my God. -How annoying.
对
Yeah.
-你为什么不跟瑞秋结婚？ -你在开玩笑吗？
-Why aren't you with Rachel? -You're kidding,right?
我们不会因为孩子的关系 就去办结婚
Look,we're not gonna be together just because we're having this baby.
我知道她不是 我上过就算的女孩…
And I know she's not just some girl I humped..
上过就算？
Oh,humped?
少来了，罗斯
Come on,Ross.
但看起来 你们两个属于彼此
But it just seems that you two belong together.
别说了，现在我无法想这件事 我得去等孩子出生
Okay,stop it. I can't deal with this right now. I have to go have a baby.
对，你还要跟谁生孩子？
Right. And with who again?
他疯了 他为什么不跟瑞秋结婚？
He's crazy. Why doesn't he wanna be with Rachel?
我知道
I know.
说真的她是个完美女性 我知道她拒绝了我…
Seriously,she's like the perfect woman. I mean,I know she turned me down..
如果她没有 她想跟我在一起…
but if she hadn't and she wanted to be with me..
我会抱着她…
I would take her in my arms and..
我有一阵子 没有这样吓你们了吧？
I haven't bummed you guys out like this in a while,have I?
-嘿 -嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
-那是谁？ -新来的人
-Who's that? -New people.
恶心夫妇怎么了？
What happened to the Disgustingtons?
他们去生孩子了 那不公平，罗斯，是我先来的
They're having their baby. It's not fair,Ross. I got here first!
你离开不久 他们就将她推进产房了
Right after you left,they wheeled her off into delivery.
但她走之前 让我看了一下她的产道
Oh,but not before she gave me a nice,juicy shot of little Jamie crowning away.
抱歉
Wow. Sorry.
新来的人怎么样？
So how are the new people?
他们帮彼此 取了很不寻常的绰号
Well,they have some unusual pet names for each other.
包括“坏心贱人”跟“病态混蛋”
Including "Evil Bitch" and "Sick Bastard."
-天啊，是阵痛 -是吗？好了，深呼吸
-Oh,gosh,a contraction. -Yeah? Okay,okay. Just breathe.
-你在看她吗？ -不
-Are you looking at her? -No!
-别看她，病态混蛋 -亲爱的，我发誓我没有看她
-Don't you look at her,you sick bastard! -Honey,I swear I wasn't looking at her!
她要生了 你喜欢吗？病态贱人
She's in labor. You like that,you sick son of a bitch?
我只是…
I'm just gonna..
看吧？那都是你偷看的关系 胖变态
See? It's because you were looking,you fat pervert.
不，我相信没有人在偷看 我们只是需要一点隐私
No,no. I'm sure no one was looking. Just want some privacy.
你想念你的女朋友吗？
You miss your girlfriend?
别理他们
Just ignore them.
-你没事吧？ -没事
-You okay? -Yeah.
-罗斯 -什么？
-Ross. -What?
-他在偷看我 -嘿
-He's looking at me. -Hey!
你想活着看到你的孩子吗？
You wanna live to see your baby?
别那样跟我丈夫说话 你这个大笨蛋
Don't you talk to my husband like that,you stupid bastard!
天啊，如果你那么想要孩子 去偷一个吧
Oh,good God! If you want a baby so bad,just go steal it!
别担心 对我们来说这些宝宝太丑了
Oh,don't worry. These babies are far too ugly for us.
你是怎么了？ 你什么时候这么喜欢孩子了？
What is going on with you. Since when are you so crazy about babies?
我不是喜欢孩子 我是为我们感到疯狂
I'm not crazy about babies. I'm crazy about us.
什么？
What?
我们总是说以后要生孩子 不是现在…
We've always talked about having babies someday,not now..
但我开始认为我们应付得来 我们准备好了
but I'm starting to think that we can handle it. We're good.
我们真的准备好了
We're really good.
我们准备齐全
We are pretty good.
但你没准备好前 我是不会行动的
But nothing has to happen until you're ready.
或许我准备好了
Well,maybe I'm ready now.
我是说它有点可怕 或许没关系
I mean,it's a little scary,but maybe it's right.
什么？才不会没关系 我们还没有准备好要生孩子
What? It's not right! We're not ready to have a kid now!
-什么？ -我是在开玩笑，这一定会很好玩
-What? -I'm kidding. This is gonna be fun.
我们要试试看吗？ 我们现在要试吗？
So we're gonna try? I mean,we're trying?
我们要试着怀孕
We're trying to get pregnant.
我不想在宝宝面前 那么做
I'm not comfortable doing this in front of the babies.
-你想什么时候开始试？ -好吧，等一下
-So when do you want to start trying? -All right,hold on a sec.
-你在算生理周期？ -对
-Period math? -Yeah.
我们可以从现在开始
Well,we could start trying now.
-在这里？ -不是
-Right here? -No,not here.
或许吧
Maybe here.
这里很完美，我们得想办法消磨时间 而且医院里有很多床
It's perfect. We got a lot of time to kill,and we're in a building that's full of beds!
它还很干净
And it's so clean!
加油，你这个笨机器
Come on,you stupid machine! Come on!
-它吃掉你的钱了吗？ -没有
-It ate your money? -No.
-那么楼下见 -好吧
-I'll see you downstairs then. -All right.
我拿到了
Hey,I got one! I got one!
-嗨 -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
-上或下？ -下楼，谢谢
-Oh,up or down? -Oh. Down,please.
我讨厌抢男人的风头 但可以由我来吗？
I hate to be a ball-buster,but can I just do it?
-麻烦你按上楼 -没问题
-Could you press up too? -Sure.
-我真的很遗憾，我也曾摔断过腿 -是吗？你怎么会摔断腿？
-I feel bad. I broke my leg once too. -Yeah? How'd yours happen?
说来话长 那有点丢脸
Well,it's a long story,it's kind of embarrassing.
那是性爱手册排版上出了点小错误
Let's just say there was a typographical error with a sex manual.
-你呢？ -车祸
-How about you? -Car accident.
有个白痴在打手机 没注意看前面？
Some idiot on a cell phone wasn't paying attention?
对，就是我
Yeah. Me.
-抱歉 -不，别那么说
-Sorry. -Oh,no. No,don't be.
没有别人受伤 我非常幸运
Nobody else got hurt. And I was pretty lucky.
我很高兴你没有大碍
Well,I,for one,am glad you made it.
是吗？你并不认识我
Are you sure? I mean,you don't know me.
我可能是被派来 摧毁地球的外星人
I could have been sent from another planet to destroy Earth.
你连“下楼”按钮都按不到 我想地球很安全
Couldn't press the "down" button. I think Earth's okay.
我的电梯来了
Oh,hey,that's me.
我想你是来探病的
Hey,I take it you're just visiting someone.
如果你有时间想拜访其他人…
Well,if you have some time and you wanna visit someone else..
对，我很乐意
Yeah,I would like that.
-太棒了，我的房号是… -等一下，什么？不，电梯
-Great. I'm in room.. -Wait! What? No! Elevator! No!
你得按下按钮才行
You gotta press the button.
护士说 他们要送另一位女人过来
The nurse said they're bringing in another woman.
她怀孕了吗？
Oh. Is she pregnant yet?
她不需要 她还是能比我更快将孩子生下来
She doesn't need to be. She'll still have the baby before I do.
-罗斯，我又阵痛了 -好吧
-Oh,Ross! Another contraction. -Oh,okay. Here,here.
没错
That's it.
-听起来好像很痛 -没错
-Oh,that sounded like a bad one. -Yeah,it was.
我的阵痛没有那么厉害 又来了
Mine haven't been so bad. Oh,here comes one now.
真的好痛
Oh,that was a big one.
那像是最痛的一次 你没事吧？亲爱的
That was,like,the biggest one yet. Are you okay,honey?
我没事
I'm okay,honey.
我有坏消息 越来越痛了
Well,I got some bad news. It gets worse.
到了最后 它们真的很痛…
And when you get to the end,they get really big..
每分钟就会来个一次
and they come,like,every minute.
我的阵痛间隔很短 我想…
Well,mine are pretty close together. I think..
-对不起 -没关系
-Excuse me. -Yeah,that's quite all right.
对了，我是乔安娜 你呢？
Oh,by the way,my name's Johanna. What's yours?
对不起，你能帮我一下吗？
Excuse me,could you help me with something?
我在找一个男人
I'm looking for a man.
谁不是呢？
Well,who isn't?
你不是
You. You aren't.
太好了
Good for you.
总之我在找 一个断了一条腿的病人
Anyway,the patient I'm looking for has a broken leg.
他坐着轮椅，31到35岁 非常迷人
He's in a wheelchair. He's early to mid-30s,very attractive.
连你都会那么想
Even you would think so.
-我知道你在说谁 -太棒了，他住几号病房？
-I know who you're talking about. -Great! What room number is he in?
抱歉 我们得对病人的资料保密
I'm sorry. Patient information is confidential.
我不会打扰他 我们刚刚说过话…
No,I'm not gonna bother him. We were talking earlier..
小姐，对不起 只有医院人员能取得资料
Ma'am,I'm sorry. That information is restricted to hospital staff.
-她跟我是一起的，德瑞克雷莫瑞医生 -哪个德瑞克医生？
-She's with me. Dr. Drake Ramoray. -Dr. Drake who?
雷莫瑞，那是葡萄牙姓 我们需要他的资料，我是医生
Ramoray. It's Portuguese. We need that information. I'm a doctor.
-这间医院的医生？ -该死，我们正在浪费宝贵的时间
-A doctor at this hospital? -Damn it,we're losing precious time.
你希望头上 沾了这男人的血…
You want this man's blood on your head..?
-是手 -手上
-Hands. -Hands!
你必须告诉我 他住几号病房
It is absolutely essential that you tell me what room he is staying in.
他是我的病人 我治疗他很多年了
He's a patient of mine. I've treated him for years.
-他住816号病房 -816，谢谢
-He's in room 816. -816. Thank you.
-他叫什么名字？ -不用
-And what is his name? -No.
-我想我们找到一个地方了 -好吧
-I think we found a place. -Okay.
等一下，你想增加一点气氛吗？
Wait. Wanna set the mood a little?
喂，莫妮卡
Hello,Monica.
-不是那样 -好吧
-Not like that. -Oh,okay.
-把灯关暗些 -好吧
-We'll dim the lights. -Okay.
或者通通关掉
Or turn them out altogether.
没有精油蜡烛 好吧，我们上吧
No scented candles. Okay,here. There we go.
好吧 给我消毒，但没关系
Okay,okay. Making me sterile,but okay.
对不起，等一下 我们有保险套吗？
Okay. I'm sorry. Oh,wait. Do we have a condom?
对了
Oh,right!
98点6度，你会没事的
Yes,98.6. You're gonna be fine.
就是这里
This is it!
-就是他 -太棒了，去找他吧
-That's him! -Great. Go get him!
等一下 或许你该先进去
Wait a second. Or maybe you could go in first.
他真的不是我喜欢的那一型
He's not really my type.
不是你，雷莫瑞医生 问他问题，看看他是什么样的人
Not you. Dr. Ramoray. Ask him questions and see what he's like.
-大家会对医生说出所有事 -你说他是个好男人
-People tell doctors everything. -You said he was this great guy.
我认识的男人一开始都很好 最后都成了大混蛋
All the guys I meet seem nice at first,then turn out to be big jerks.
-你的确吸引了一些烂男人 -对，我知道
-You do attract some stinkers. -Yeah,I know.
朗医生 我已经等了17个小时
Dr. Long,I've been at this for 17 hours.
三个女人被推进来 又被推出去生下了孩子
Three women have come and gone with their babies.
你得给我好消息 我张开了几公分？八？九？
You gotta give me good news. How many centimeters am I dilated? Eight? Nine?
-三 -只有三公分？
-Three. -Just three?
我才张开了三公分
I'm dilated three!
虽然进度有点慢 放心，你做的很好
We are moving along just slowly. Don't worry,you're doing great.
-我马上回来 -谢谢
-I'll be back soon. -Thank you.
你知道吗？我不等 我要把孩子生出来
You know what? I'm not waiting. I'm gonna push this baby out.
我要那么做，三公分 大概是这么大吧？
I'm doing it. Three centimeters. That's gotta be like this,right?
-事实上是这么大 -愚蠢的度量衡系统
-Actually,it's more like this. -Oh,stupid metric system.
我们得直接将你推到产房
We're gonna need to take you straight to the delivery room.
我的天啊
Oh,for the love of God!
孩子要出来了
It's coming! It's coming!
她生了
And here it is!
天啊
Oh,come on!
我是德瑞克雷莫瑞医生 我得问你几个例行的问题
I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray. I have a few routine questions I need to ask you.
真的吗？一直是威尔斯医生在治疗我
Really? I've been dealing with Dr. Wells.
我是说，我是神经科医生 为了预防万一…
I know. I'm a neurologist. Just to be on the safe side..
威尔斯医生需要更多相关资料 所以他请我过来
Dr. Wells wanted a more comprehensive overview. So he sent me.
威尔斯医生是女的
Dr. Wells is a woman!
我是在考你，反应不错
That was a test. Good response.
-好吧，全名 -克利夫伯奈特
-All right. Full name? -Clifford Burnett.
-生日 -1968年11月16日
-Date of birth? -November 16,1968.
年龄
Age?
-你不会自己算吗？ -我是医生，不是数学家
-Can't you figure that out? -I'm a doctor,not a mathematician.
-33岁 -好吧
-I'm 33. -Okay.
-已婚吗？ -不
-And are you married? -No.
真的吗？33岁还是单身？ 你害怕许下承诺？
Oh,really? So 33 and single? Would you say you have commitment issues?
所有的问题都是私人问题吗？
Are all the questions this personal?
对
Yes.
如果你想知道的话，我是鳏夫
Well,if you must know,I'm a widower.
-太可怕了，我真的很遗憾 -对
-Oh,that's terrible. I'm really sorry. -Yeah.
我太太五年前 因为轻度心肌梗塞过世
I lost my wife five years ago to a mild cardial infarction.
-她得了心脏病，医生 -对，轻度心…
-A heart attack,doctor. -Oh,yeah. Well,yeah,mild car..
你会头晕吗？
Are you experiencing any dizziness?
不会
No.
-疼痛有加剧吗？ -没有
-Has the pain been getting worse? -No.
你会跟女人上了床后 不再打电话给她们吗？
Do you sleep with women and never call them again?
-不会 -太棒了
-No. -Excellent. Excellent.
最后是 你有奇怪的性癖好吗？
And finally,are you into any weird stuff,you know,sexually?
-没有 -答错了
-No! -Wrong answer.
-这个房间是空的 -好吧，等一下，听我说
-This room's available. -Okay! Wait,you listen to me!
已经有四个女人…
Since I have been waiting,four women..
一共是四个 比我子宫颈张开的公分数还多一个
that's four,one higher than the number of centimeters I'm dilated..
进来这里，又被推出去生孩子 下一个是我，轮到我了，那才公平
have come and gone with their babies. I'm next. It's my turn. It's only fair.
如果你再推个女人进来 她又比我先生，我要告你
If you bring in one more woman who has her baby before me,I will sue you.
不是这家医院，我要告你 我先生是律师
Not this hospital. I'm gonna sue you. My husband is a lawyer.
-瑞秋 -你别管这件事
-Rach? -You get back on that case,honey!
我想下一位产妇 不会太快生
I don't think the next patient is very far along.
好吧，把她推进来
Okay. Well,then bring her in.
我的天啊
Oh,my God!
我不敢相信
I can't believe this!
但这是真的
And yet,somehow,it's true.
我是说这太棒了 我们可以指腹为婚
I mean,this is so great. We're gonna be baby buddies!
把你的双腿并拢 别让宝宝听见了
Squeeze your legs together and cover the baby's ears.
-嗨，亲爱的 -嗨，亲爱的
-Hi,sweetie! -Hi,sweetheart.
他是我丈夫希德，你们应该没见过他 罗斯，瑞秋，他是希德
This is my husband,Sid. I don't think you've met him. Ross,Rachel,this is Sid.
一年前我在皮肤科诊所 认识他
I nabbed him a year ago at the dermatologist's office.
还好我长了成人型青春痘
Thank God for adult acne!
我还是不敢相信 我是全世界最幸运的人
I still can't believe it. I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
真的吗？
Really?
他说什么？
What'd he say?
你得大声一点 他几乎快聋了
You have to speak very loudly,he's almost completely deaf.
-没错 -那当然
-Oh,there you go. -Of course he is.
恭喜你们 我不知道你们结婚了
Congratulations,you two. I didn't even know you got married.
-我们没结婚 -什么？
-Oh,we didn't. -What?
我们只是要生下我们的孩子 就是那样
We're just having this baby together,but that's all,you know.
为什么？
Why?
我们还没有到那个程度，知道吗？ 但我们很期待宝宝的出生
We're just not in that place,you know? But we're very excited about this.
那样我就没话说了
Oh. Well,then shut me up.
告诉我我该怎么做
Just tell me how.
我又开始阵痛了
Oh,I feel another one coming.
希德，你这个幸运的聋子
Sid,you lucky,deaf bastard.
-还有呢？ -他33岁
-What else? What else? -He's 33.
是个鳏夫
A widower.
他似乎是个标准男人 他没有奇怪的性癖好
He seemed like a standup guy. And he's not into anything weird sexually.
菲比要出马了
Enter Phoebe!
我们该告诉瑞秋 她隔壁就有一间单人待产室吗？
Should we tell Rachel there's an empty private room right next door to hers?
没错，或许我们可以在这里做爱
We could. Or we could have sex in it.
让我边脱裤子边想
Well,let me think about that while I remove my pants!
好吧，先生，让我受孕吧
Okay,mister! Fertilize me!
那是珍妮丝的声音吗？
Does that sound like Janice?
如果不是的话，就是有个人很像她
If it's not,then there's two of them.
那表示世界末日到了
And that would mean it's the end of the world!
嘿
Hey.
-嘿 -嗨
-Hey. -Hi.
我不敢相信要这么久 你还好吗？
I can't believe this is taking so long. How you doing?
还不错，你知道试着 将圣伯纳犬从屁股推出来的感觉吗？
Not bad. You know that feeling,trying to blow a Saint Bernard out your ass?
很快会有人叫她“妈”
And soon someone will call her "Mom."
真的太奇怪了，我听到…
Weirdest thing. Did I hear..?
上帝他母亲的，是真的
Mother of God,it's true!
钱德宾
Chandler Bing!
珍妮丝
Janice.
不只那样，珍妮丝要生了 她正在阵痛
Not just Janice. Janice in labor. Contracting and everything.
这应该很容易 我的骨盆很宽
Oh,this should be easy. I have a very wide pelvis.
你应该记得的，钱德
You remember,Chandler.
我为你感到难过
I feel so bad for you.
她是你的前女友，我前男友是理查
She's your ex. And I have Richard.
珍妮丝 我不知道你怀孕了
Janice,I didn't even know you were pregnant.
你偷走了哪个笨蛋的心？
Who's the unwitting human whose essence you've stolen?
这是你的孩子
It's you.
This is yours.
什么？
What?
看他有多紧张 我们好几年没上过床了
Look how nervous he gets! We haven't slept together in years!
那真的很有趣，会痛吗？ 生产会痛吗？
That's funny. Does it hurt? Does the labor hurt?
好吧，我想到一个 如果非吃不可，你要吃哪一个？
Okay,I've got one for you. If you had to,which would you eat?
千里眼的小狗或会说话的猩猩？
A Seeing Eye dog or a talking gorilla?
我猜是会说话的猩猩
I'd have to say the talking gorilla.
因为至少我可以跟他解释 是你逼我吃掉他
Because at least I could explain to him that you're making me eat him.
-有人念过大学 -对
-Oh. Somebody went to college. -Yeah.
怎么了？对不起
Wow. What is it? I'm sorry.
对不起，我的脚好痒
I'm sorry. My foot itches like crazy.
让我来吧
Oh. I'll get it.
通常我会跟女人混熟后 才会让她用汤匙帮我搔痒
I usually get to know a girl better before I let her spoon me.
别激动，它不是叉子
Relax. It's not like we're forking.
太棒了
When. When.
谢谢，听着
Thank you. Listen.
你一定是个汤匙高手
You seem to really know what to do with a utensil.
你愿意跟我共进晚餐吗？
Would you like to go to dinner sometime?
-我很乐意 -是吗？
-Yeah,I'd really like that. -Yeah?
对，我发誓不会逼你吃聪明的动物
Yeah. And I promise I won't make you eat any remarkable animals.
我在想…
I was thinking..
我想追求你
I'd kind of like to make a move.
但我的腿不方便
But,you know,with the leg.
对
Oh,yeah.
或许需要一点帮忙
Maybe a little help.
好吧
Okay.
我来帮你拉枕头
Let me fix your pillow.
克利夫，你太猴急了
Cliff,you're so forward.
很高兴认识你们
Oh,it was really nice meeting you.
希德
Sid!
那是我第一次听到她的声音
That's the first time I heard her voice.
我不在乎
I didn't care for it.
一共是五个，罗斯 五个女人生了五个孩子…
Oh,that's five,Ross. Five women have had five babies..
我还是没生
and I have had no babies.
她为什么不肯出来？
Why doesn't she want to come out?
你知道我在想什么吗？ 我想九个月来…
You know what I think it is? I think you made such a nice home for her..
她在你的身体里很舒服 所以她不想离开
over the last nine months that she just doesn't want to leave.
你甚至在瞎掰哄我
Oh,look at you making up crap for me.
-天啊 -好吧
-Oh,God. -Okay. Okay.
21小时，你是英雄
Twenty-one hours. You're a hero.
医生，你得想想办法 给我药…
Doctor,you gotta do something! Get me drugs..
或是放火 把她熏出来
or light a fire up in there and just smoke it out!
事实上 我想你可以进产房了
Actually,I think you're ready to go to the delivery room.
什么？
What?
开了10公分了 你快当妈妈了
Ten centimeters. You're about to become a mom.
天啊，好吧
Oh,my God. Okay.
打败你了，混蛋，宝贝
Beat you,sucker! Oh,baby.
这是刚刚你拿来 帮我搔痒的汤匙吗？
Is this the same spoon that was in my cast?
你知道吗？
You know what?
这支才是
This one is.
天啊 他就是刚刚来看过我的医生
Oh,my God! That's the doctor who was in my room before.
那一定是医院里的 闭路电视系统
Well,it must be one of those closed-circuit hospital channels.
不，那是肥皂剧
No,no. That's a soap opera.
这是家充满戏剧性的医院
This is a very dramatic hospital.
我是说 电视里的那个人刚刚来过…
I'm telling you,the guy from that show was here..
还问了我一些怪问题
asking me all these weird questions.
好吧，幻想先生
Okay,Mr. Percocet.
我发誓就是他
I swear to you,that's the guy.
好吧，克利夫
Okay,Cliff.
你真的相信电视明星 来过你的房间？
Do you really believe that a character from a TV show was here in your room?
很可能是你在看电视 结果睡着了…
What probably happened was you were watching this,you drifted off to sleep..
你梦到他来过这里
and you dreamt he was here.
瑞秋要生了
Rachel's having her baby!
身为神经科医生的我 没有兴趣，我…
Which is of no interest to me as a neurologist. I..
就是他，你认识他？
That's him! You know him?
醒一醒，克利夫
Wake up,Cliff!
发生了什么事？
What is going on?
好吧，我…好吧
Okay. Okay. I.. Okay.
我派我朋友乔伊 来调查你
I sent my friend,Joey,in here to find out stuff about you.
如果…如果你想知道的话 我们觉得你是个好人
If it.. You know,if it helps,you came off great.
比现在的我好多了
A lot better than I'm coming off right now.
我不敢相信 你要他假扮医生？
I don't believe this. You got him to pretend he was a fake doctor?
假扮？对不起，喂
Fake? Excuse me? Hello?
-你要我以为自己疯了？ -那是不对的，我非常抱歉
-You tried making me think I was crazy? -That was wrong. I'm so sorry.
那只是因为我非常喜欢你 我们能重新开始吗？
It's just that I liked you so much. Can we just start over?
我不那么认为
I don't think so.
我可以说话吗？ 你跟我透露了很多你的私事
If I may? You told me a lot of personal stuff about you,right?
或许你应该知道 一些关于她的私事
Now,maybe it would help if you knew some personal stuff about her.
她曾跟男同志冰舞选手结婚
She was married to a gay ice dancer.
她帮她弟弟 生下三胞胎
She gave birth to her brother's triplets.
她的双胞胎姐姐是A片演员
Her twin sister used to do porn.
-我们不想听那些疯狂的事 -对
-We're trying to dial down the crazy. -Right.
我们并不认识彼此 要忘了这些很容易…
We don't really know each other,so it'd be easy to forget about this..
但我们对彼此有感觉 我不知道你是怎么样…
but there's something between us. I don't know about you..
但我不是常常遇到这种事
but that doesn't happen to me a lot.
-我也是 -我也是
-It doesn't happen to me either. -Me neither!
-瑞秋要生了 -对
-The baby! Rachel! -Right,right!
我喜欢这场戏
Oh,I love this scene.
听着，我也得走了
Okay,look. I gotta go too.
但…你觉得呢？ 我们能一起吃晚餐吗？
But.. What do you say? Can we just have that dinner?
三胞胎
The triplets.
你跟你弟弟没有…
You and your brother didn't..?
不，他们植入了胚胎
No! No,they implanted embryos.
-那么我们可以去吃晚餐 -太棒了
-Then dinner sounds great. -Great! Okay.
好吧，待会见
All right,then I'll see you later.
我们的朋友要生了
Our friend's having a baby.
-那是她自己的孩子？ -对
-Her own? -Oh,yeah. Yeah.
不，她真的很传统
No,she's really old-fashioned.
用力 你得再用力推五秒
Push. Push. We're gonna push for five more seconds.
五，四…
Five,four..
三，二，一
Three,two,one! Oh!
下一次阵痛 是20秒后
The next contraction should be in about 20 seconds.
-我没办法再用力了 -你表现的很好
-I can't push anymore! -You're doing great.
天啊，还要20秒耶
Oh,God! Twenty seconds,my ass!
来吧，继续用力
Here we go. Okay,keep pushing.
-来吧 -推，等一下
-Come on. -Push. Wait.
-我看到东西了 -什么？真的吗？我的天啊
-I see something. -What,you do? You do? Oh,my God!
-别说“我的天啊”，什么？ -那是什么？
-Don't say "Oh,my God!" What?! -What is that?
宝宝的屁股，她倒过来了
The baby's buttocks. She's breech.
-我以为她有两个头 -天啊
-I thought she had two heads. -Oh,God!
她没事吧？
Is she gonna be okay?
-她没事的 -好吧
-She's gonna be fine. -Okay.
她的胎位不正 你得更用力推
She's in a more difficult position,so you have to push harder now.
-好吧 -就是那样，推
-Okay. -That's it. Push. Push.
你得更用力推
You're gonna have to push even harder.
-抱歉，我办不到 -不，我知道你办得到
-I'm sorry,I can't! I can't! -Yes,you can. I know you can do this.
我不知道 拜托，帮我推吧
I had no idea. Please,you do it for me!
来吧，再一次 最后一次，准备好了吗？一，二，三
Let's go. One more time. One final push. Ready? One,two,three.
很好
Good.
继续用力
Keep pushing!
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
你不知道那有多痛
You have no idea how much this hurts.
继续用力
Keep going! Keep going!
好了
Here we go!
宝宝胎位不正，但她要出来了
She's upside down,but she's coming!
-天啊 -我的天啊
-Oh,God! -Oh! Oh,my God!
天啊，她出来了
Oh,my God,she's here.
她太完美了
Oh,she's perfect.
哇，她好小
Oh,wow! Oh,she's so tiny.
-她要去哪里？ -他们得先把她包起来
-Where'd she go? -They're just wrapping her up.
好吧，小心一点 她真的很小
Okay. Well,be careful with her,she's really tiny.
来吧
Here she is.
谢谢你终于出来了
Oh,thanks for coming out of me.
我知道
I know. Oh.
她在看我，嗨，我认识你
She's looking at me. Hi. I know you.
-你们取好名字了吗？ -还没有
-Do we have a name yet? -No,not yet.
没关系 先叫她格林之女
That's fine. For now we'll just call her Baby Girl Greene.
不，盖勒格林之女
Oh,no. Baby Girl Geller-Greene.
嗨，小女孩
Hello,Baby Girl.
-我们能进去吗？ -请进
-Can we come in? -Oh,come on in.
-她在那里 -她好漂亮
-Oh,there she is. -Oh,she's so beautiful.
来吧
Here.
天啊，她好神奇
Oh,my God. She's amazing.
我很高兴 你们喝醉后上了床
Oh,I'm so glad you guys got drunk and had sex.
太不可思议了 前一分钟她还在你肚子里…
It's incredible. I mean,one minute she's inside you..
47小时后她就出现了
and then 47 hours later,here she is.
她看起来好真实
She looks so real.
你们了解我的意思
You know what I mean.
她是个小宝贝
She's this whole tiny little person.
她已经有眼睫毛 膝盖跟…
And she already has eyelashes and knees and..
-什么？ -不，没事
-What? -Oh,no,no. It's okay.
刚刚我以为她有六根手指 但有一根是另一只手的，没事
For a second,I counted six fingers,but one was from the other hand. So we're good.
-好了，轮到我了 -菲比阿姨
-Okay,my turn. My turn. -Aunt Phoebe.
宝贝，你好可爱
Oh,baby. Oh,you're so cute!
我可以捏碎你小小的头
Oh,I could squeeze your little head.
我不会那么做的
I won't.
-亲爱的，怎么了？ -没事，我只是不由自主地哭了
-Honey,what's the matter? -Nothing. I just can't stop crying.
医生说这很正常 都是荷尔蒙害的，而且还会睡不着
The doctor said it's normal,with all the hormones,plus you're sleep-deprived.
你们都会失眠
So. You guys are all sleep-deprived.
我没看过你因为鞋子穿错脚 就哭个不停
I don't see you weeping because you put your slippers on the wrong feet.
天啊
Oh,God.
-怎么了？ -我又想起来了
-What's the matter now? -I was reliving it.
你们帮她 取好名字了吗？
Do you know what you're gonna call her yet?
等一下，她不是叫女孩吗？ 我觉得那个名字很有创意
Wait,it's not gonna be Baby Girl? I thought that was so original.
事实上 我们正在考虑两个名字
Actually,we've narrowed it down to two names.
你知道吗？两个名字我都很喜欢 你们帮忙挑一个
And you know what? I love them both. So just pick one,and that'll be it.
好吧，大伙们…
Wow,okay. Everyone..
她是伊莎贝拉
this is lsabella.
-嗨，伊莎贝拉 -嗨
-Hi,lsabella! -Hi.
什么？
What?
那不是她的名字
That's not her name.
抱歉 她感觉上不像伊莎贝拉
I'm sorry,she just doesn't feel like an lsabella.
我猜弗迪南出局了
So then I guess Ferdinand is out.
-另一个名字是什么？ -黛利拉（《圣经》中参孙的情妇,后出卖参孙）
-What was the other one? -Delilah.
太棒了 突然间她成了圣经里的妓女
Oh,great! Suddenly she sounds like a biblical whore.
我猜还是叫她女孩吧
So I guess we're back to Baby Girl.
我们该怎么办？
What are we gonna do?
-没关系，你们会想到好名字的 -你说的倒容易
-It's okay. You'll find a name. -Easy for you to say.
你已经知道 你的孩子要叫什么名字了
You already know what your kids' names will be.
-是吗？ -我14岁时就帮他们取好了名字
-You do? -I had them picked out since I was 14.
不，你的宝宝会以点心 或烘烤食物的名字来命名吧？
Oh,no,it's gonna be named after some snack or baked good,isn't it?
-告诉我们你想了什么名字 -好吧，如果是男孩的话就叫丹尼尔
-Well,tell us,what are they? -Okay. If it's a boy,it's Daniel.
-如果是女孩呢？ -我不想说
-And if it's a girl? -I don't wanna say.
少来了，告诉我们 我们不会抢走它的
Oh,stop. Tell us. We're not gonna want it.
好吧，她叫艾玛
Okay. It's Emma.
艾玛
Emma.
看吧，我不喜欢它
See,I don't want it.
你还想到其他你不会用的 完美名字吗？
Do you have any other totally perfect names that you're not gonna use?
-拿去吧 -什么？
-Take it. -What?
她真的很适合叫艾玛
She's clearly an Emma.
亲爱的，但你喜欢那个名字
Oh,honey,but you love that name.
对，但我更爱你
Yeah,but I love you more.
而且什么名字都跟宾不配 所以我是死定了
Besides,nothing goes with Bing. So I'm screwed.
嗨，艾玛
Hi,Emma.
对，就是你
Yep,that's you.
你是我们的小艾玛
You're our little Em.
怎么了？亲爱的
What's that,honey?
什么？
What?
你要个小表妹？
Oh,you want a little cousin?
你现在就要？
You want a cousin right now?
你们觉得 我看起来像个大精子或…
Do I look like a giant sperm to all of you,or..?
（清洁间）
-那真的是太神奇了 -我知道
-That was amazing. -I know.
你知道我们很可能 已经永远地改变了我们的生活吗？
Hey,do you realize that we may have just changed our lives forever?
我们可能已经开始组成了我们的家庭 九个月后我们可能会来这里…
We may have started our family. In nine months we could be here..
生下我们的孩子
having our own baby.
要是没办法的话 我们得把宝宝生在桶子里
And if not,we got to do it on a bucket.
我非常爱你
I love you so much.
-是吗？ -对
-Oh,yeah? -Yeah.
你想再做一次吗？
You wanna do it again?
这次是为了我们？
This time just for us?
或许吧
Probably.
亚朗利普曼古拉尼克 要跟他未来的新娘打个招呼
Aaron Lipman-Guralnick would like to say hello to his future bride.
他真的会让人说不出话来 对吧？
Wow,he kind of takes your breath away,doesn't he?
他是个谦虚的人
He's a keeper.
看看那个小可爱
Look at the little munchkin.
别担心 当你大到可以跟他约会时…
Don't you worry. By the time you're old enough to date him..
他会有个不一样的鼻子
he's gonna have a different nose.
-你觉得如何？ -我很好
-How you feeling? -Oh,I'm fine.
我真的很佩服你做的事 你要自己抚养她
I really admire what you're doing. Just raising her all alone.
我不是一个人，我有罗斯
I'm not doing it alone. I have Ross.
现在是的，如果他认识别人结了婚 那时又会是怎么样的呢？
Sure. Now. But what happens when he meets somebody else and gets married?
他会离婚的 那就是罗斯
Well,then he gets a divorce. It's Ross.
我得告诉你，瑞秋，听珍妮丝的话
I'm telling you,Rachel,listen to Janice.
男人都说他们会在 但他们会成立自己的家庭
They all say they're gonna be there,until they start their real family.
-罗斯不会那么做的 -以前我也那么相信
-That's never gonna happen with Ross. -That's what I thought.
如果我的孩子能跟她爸 及新的波霸小姐共度一个周末…
I'm lucky if my kid gets to spend a weekend with her father..
那算我运气好
and little Miss New Boobs.
真的吗？
Really?
我讨厌跟你这么说…
I hate to be the one to say it..
但你们两个得靠自己
but,honey,you two are on your own.
那是…你知道的，那是…
Well,that's.. You know,that's..
我们已经单独相处了20分钟 我们表现的很好
We've been alone for the last 20 minutes and we're doing okay.
或许我们不会孤单的
Maybe we won't be alone.
因为最近 我跟罗斯之间有些事发生
Because lately things have been happening between me and Ross.
我来医院前 我们还接了吻，你知道吗？
And right before I went into labor,we had this kiss. You know?
或许那会是个开始
So it might be the beginning of something.
-嗨，珍妮丝 -嗨
-Hey,Janice. -Oh,hi.
这个小家伙是谁？
Who's this little guy?
-亚朗，那是你未来的岳父 -不
-Aaron,your future son-in-law. -Oh,no,no.
不
No.
-我让你们一家人好好独处 -好吧
-I'm gonna leave you three alone. -Okay.
天啊，你看到那孩子的鼻子了吗？
Man,you see the kid on that nose?
你知道我刚刚想到什么吗？
You know what I was thinking about?
我们出门前的那个吻 那真的很特别吧？
That kiss before we left the apartment. That was something,huh?
对，真的是
Yeah. Yeah,it really was.
但我们…我们得小心点
But we.. We gotta be careful.
我们…你知道的 我们不能让历史重演
We.. You know,we can't let that happen again,you know?
对
Right.
-我们不希望再发生那种事 -对，所以我才会跟你提这件事
-We don't want to go down that road. -No. That's why I brought it up.
-他们没有汽水吗？ -天啊，对不起
-They didn't have any sodas? -Oh,my God. I'm sorry.
我忙着跟护士说话 完全忘了
I was talking to this nurse. Completely forgot.
现在就已经开始了
And so it begins.
她在里面吗？
She in there?
对，护士正把她放在床上 那就是她
Yeah. She's putting her down now. That's her.
每个宝宝都很漂亮 那真的很神奇吧？
Isn't it amazing how every baby is beautiful?
除了那个以外
Except that one.
这是什么？宠物动物园吗？
What is this? A petting zoo?
你看，快看艾玛
Look. Look at Emma.
我无法决定 她长得像你或瑞秋
I can't decide who she looks like,you or Rachel.
什么？你在开玩笑吗？ 她美极了，完全是瑞秋的遗传
Oh,what,are you kidding? She's gorgeous! It's all Rachel.
对不起，这是我最后一次问你 你们两个为什么不结婚？
I'm sorry. For the last time,why aren't you two together again?
不，我知道 因为你们没有到那个程度
No,I know. Because you're not in that place.
那真的很棒 但事实上你们真的到了
Which would be fine,except you totally are.
情况很复杂，好吗？
It's complicated,okay?
对，那是真的
Yeah,that's true.
你一直都爱着她 你们生了一个孩子
You love her,you always have,you have a child together.
没有答案是百分之百的正确
There's no right answer.
我们曾经交往过 后来分手，复合后又分手
Look,we've been together. Then apart. Then together,then apart.
现在我们生了一个孩子
And now we have a baby.
如果我们又复合 结果还是不行…
It's just,if we got together again and it didn't work out..
我不会对艾玛那么做
I could never do that to Emma.
她来到这个世界 想像每件事都…这是我的想法
I mean,she came into this world thinking everything.. Now me.
什么？ 他们在水里放东西？
What,do they put something in the water here?
瑞秋跟我 现在过得很好
It's just,Rachel and l,we're doing really well now.
我知道，如果你想更进一步 就得突破现状
I know. If you try to make it more,you might wreck it.
-没错 -对
-Yeah,exactly. -Right.
或许你可以得到 你从15岁开始梦想的世界
Or you might get everything you've wanted since you were 15.
嘿
Hey.
我看到一个女人 同时在喂双胞胎母乳
I saw a woman breast-feeding twins at the same time.
那真的很像怪物秀
It is like a freak show up here.
-怎么了？ -没事
-What's the matter? -Nothing.
怎么了？嘿
What is it? Hey.
-真的没事，我… -瑞秋，别这样，什么？
-Really,it's nothing. I'm.. -Rach,come on. What?
我一直在想 我跟宝宝要怎么独自活下去
I've just been thinking about how my baby and I are gonna be all alone.
你在说什么？罗斯呢？
What are you talking about? What about Ross?
拜托，他会有自己的家庭 双胞胎跟新波霸小姐
Please. He'll be with his real family. The twins and little Miss New Boobs.
好吧 我看那个女人多久了？
Okay,how long was I watching that woman?
我那么说…
I'm just saying that,you know..
因为有一天 罗斯会认识别人…
someday Ross is gonna meet somebody..
他会去过自己的生活
and he's gonna have his own life.
对吧？
Right?
我猜你说的对
Yeah,I guess so.
我没有想过 我要自己抚养这个宝宝
I just never thought I'd be raising this baby all by myself.
那真的很傻吧？
That's pretty dumb,huh?
你得听我说，听着
Hey,you listen to me. Listen to me.
你永远都不会是一个人
You are never,ever gonna be alone.
好吧？ 我发誓我不会让那种事发生
Okay? I promise I won't let that happen.
乔伊，喔，亲爱的 没有你我该怎么办？
Joey. Oh,sweetie,what would I do without you?
你不必担心，好吗？
You don't have to worry about that,okay?
你能再帮我 拿盒面纸来吗？
Could you grab me my other box of tissues?
-就在罗斯的外套下面 -没问题
-They're under Ross' coat. -Sure.
我的天啊
Oh,my God!
乔伊
Joey?
我的天啊
Oh,my God.
好吧
Okay.